wallpapermaiden.com 2019-12-11

# Privacy Policy - WallpaperMaiden

Your privacy is extremely important to us

At WallpaperMaiden (“wallpapermaiden.com”, “Website”, “we”, “our”, or “us”), we are committed to protecting the information provided to us by our users, including but not limited to visitors to our Website, and users who download wallpapers from our Website (“users” or “you”). It is our policy to respect the privacy of individuals and the confidentiality of information provided by our users. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) outlines how we collect, disclose, use, store and handle personal information provided by our users.

Consent

By accessing our Website and/or submitting your personal information to us through any other means, you are consenting to the processing of your personal information and to our collection, use, disclosure, storage and handling of your personal information, as set out in this Policy. You are entitled to withdraw your consent at any time; however, we may not then be able to provide you with our full range of services. In case you are under 18 or the applicable age of maturity in your jurisdiction, we require a parent or a guardian to consent to this Policy and the Terms of Service of this Website.

Updates and Amendments

This Policy will be updated, reviewed and amended from time to time, at the sole discretion of wallpapermaiden.com. Material changes (if any) to this Policy will be indicated by notice on our home page. Please check this Policy regularly to be aware of any updates and changes. Any information collected, used, disclosed, stored or handled by us will be governed by the latest version of this Policy. Continued use of this Website, or use of any of the services offered, will thereafter constitute your deemed acceptance of the revised Policy.

Information we collect about you

At WallpaperMaiden, we collect information which are essential for providing a better and more efficient wallpaper browsing and downloading experience to you. Information we may collect includes any information which you might fill up on the Website by subscribing to any of the services offered on the site including our ability to send you promotional emails, any information provided to us by means of enquiry or correspondence (including but not limited to email, social media, telephone or fax), and the details of your downloads (together, “Personal Information”). In case you do not wish disclose any such Personal Information, please do not directly provide us with any Personal Information though any method (including but not limited to the methods listed above) of communication.

Cookies and anonymous information

Our website uses cookies to record anonymous information for analytics and other purposes, which helps us improve our website’s experience continuously. Please change your browser settings if you do not wish to accept cookies. Such information may include anonymous information which is automatically logged each time you visit our Website, including the type of browser you are using, the server name and IP address, the pages you access, or the source from which you linked to wallpapermaiden.com Website (together, “Anonymous Information”). In this Policy, “Personal Information” and “Anonymous Information” are together called “Information”.

Why do we need your Information and who do we disclose it to?

At WallpaperMaiden, we need your Information to provide users a seamless browsing and downloading experience on our Website, and to efficiently manage any enquiries, requests or complaints that you may have. We may disclose your Information to our subcontractors, subsidiaries, affiliates or third party advertisers, service providers (including those hosting and managing our Website, providing customer service, marketing and advertising and other related services), and sponsors who administer our promotions. Information can be used to manage downloads, for promotions or surveys, to conduct research and analysis, and otherwise protect users, guests or our Website. Also, in case as and when WallpaperMaiden’s business develops and all or some of its corporate assets are acquired, and customer information is one of the transferred assets, Information may be one of the assets transferred. Further, Information you may provide may be necessary for any legislative, contractual or reporting obligations that we may have, or to respond to questions that we receive from any public authority, or to enforce WallpaperMaiden’s Terms of Service and other agreements.

Protection of Personal Information

All Information that you provide to wallpapermaiden.com is kept in secure computer storage facilities. We take reasonable steps to protect all such Information from unauthorised access, misuse, interference and loss, modification, alteration, destruction or disclosure. Information and records may be required to be maintained by us for a considerable period of time. However, when the Information is no longer needed, or upon your request, we will remove any details you have provided us with, or will securely destroy the records.

Enquiries and Complaints

You can make enquiries regarding your Information, access to, correction or deletion of such Information, request further information on this Policy, withdraw consent for use and disclosure of Information, unsubscribe from our mailing lists or newsletters, or complain of breaches of this Policy by writing to us at: [contact](https://www.wallpapermaiden.com/contact "contact") page

For any of the above requirements, you can also contact us directly at: [contact](https://www.wallpapermaiden.com/contact "contact") page

We aim to acknowledge receipt of all enquiries and respond to them within a reasonable time. Complaints (if any) need to be accompanied by sufficient supporting evidence, so that we can process them successfully. We may request you to provide additional information which might assist us in our investigation. We will respond to your complaints within a reasonable time.

This Policy was last updated on Feb 24 2017.
